[Opening Music]
[musica introductoria]
Hey and welcome to the course! Well done getting started! If it's been
Hola y bienvenido al curso! Muy bien por empezar!,si ha pasado un tiempo
a little while since you watched the promo video above, then take a quick look,
desde que que viste el video promocional de arriba, echa un vistazo porque
because it gives you a great overview of the course. In just a few minutes we'll start
te da una vista general del curso. En unos minutos empezaremos
downloading and installing Unreal. Before we do that, I just want to talk about the structure
descargando e instalando Unreal. Antes de hacerlo , quiero hablar de la estructura del
of the course for you. Firstly, attached to this video and
curso para ti, Primero, adjunto a este video y
the talking head video, at the start of every section, are the section
el primero , el principio de cada sección, están las notas de la sección
notes. Now, that is a .pdf that you can take and
Es un pdf que puede descargar
copy off, print out if you must, but consider the tress, maybe don't print.
imprimir si debes, pero recuerda a los árboles, quizá no imprimas
Maybe just take electronic notes, on those slides,
A lo mejor toma notas digitalmente, en las diapositivas
and it's a copy of all the slides that I use in the course and gives you plenty of
y es una copia de todas las diapositivas que uso en el curso, y te da la opción
opportunity to take your own notes and make your own annotations, etc.
de tomar tus propias notas y apuntes, etc...
So, that's that there attached! Please download those and start using those.
Asi que esto esta ahi adjunto. Por favor descargalos y empieza a usarlos.
I want to talk about the people who get the most from this course, and of course,
Quiero hablarte de la gente que aprovecha al máximo el curso, y por supuesto
the people who get the most from the course are the people who put the most into the course.
estos son los que más se aprovechan de él
So, make sure you're one of those people! Participate heavily
Asegurate de ser uno de ellos!. Participa mucho
in the discussions. Try and answer other students' questions.
en las discusiones. Intenta responder las preguntas de otros
Ask good questions yourself. Share your progress and your fears and your
Haz buenas preguntas. Comparte tu progreso y miedos y
concerns and your successes and your failures, and just
tus preocupaciones y éxitos y fracasos, y
put a little bit extra in. Do what I do in the videos, but also
solo pon un poco mas de esfuerzo. Haz lo que hago en los videos, pero también
do some other stuff. Just explore and enjoy the course and you'll
haz otras cosas. Solo explora y disfruta el curso, y
get absolutely tons out of it. And support, what
sacaras muchisimo de este. Y ayudas, que
support to expect? Well, I'll be in the community support forums,
ayuda esperas? Pues, estaré en los foros de la comunidad
most weekdays. Not very often on the weekend, but Monday to
la mayoría de los días de semana. No mucho los findes, pero de Lunes a
Friday I'll be there most days, I'll pop in. And the most important thing,
Viernes estaré la mayoría de los días. Y lo más importante,
however, is to support each other. And the way to do that firstly is to
sin embargo es apoyarse entre vosotros. Y el modo de hacerlo es
ask very good questions, and just make sure that if you are on the other side
preguntando buenas preguntas, y asegurandote que si estas en el otro lado de la valla
of the fence that you would have a chance of answering the question. Make it as short
tendrás la oportunidad de responder a la pregunta. Hazla lo mas corta possible
as possible, your question, but as long as necessary. And talking about being on the other side
,tu pregunta, pero tan larga como sea necesaria. Y hablando de estar al otro lado de la valla
of the fence, help answer other peoples' questions. Even if you don't know the answer,
, ayuda respondiendo las preguntas de otros . Incluso si no sabes la respuesta,
start the conversation! You know, imagine you're there stuck taking your course,
empieza la conversación! Sabes, imagina que estás atrancado en el curso,
and you ask a question. It's great if another student comes back to you
y haces una pregunta. Esta muy bien si otro estudiante viene
really quickly. So, the best way to encourage that is for you to be one of those people,
rapidamente. Y, la mejor manera de motivar esto es que tu seas una de esas personas
that responds to questions of the students really fast! I will, of course,
que responde las preguntas de los estudiantes muy rápido! Yo, por supuesto,
come in very regularly and help keep the conversation on track.
vendré a menudo a ayudar a mantener la conversación fluyendo.
Please respond to each other's questions. Try and help each other out.
Por favor responded os unos a otros. Intended ayudaros
The only other thing to say is, what happens if you're more experienced?
La única otra cosa a decir es, que pasa si tienes más experiencia?
Well, if you're a more experienced user, then have a look through the
Bueno, si sabes más, echa un vistazo a las
sections of the course, and find the first section that you think would
secciones del curso, y encuentra la primera sección que pienses
be a real challenge for you. And then, just try and do that one as quickly
que sea un reto para ti. Entonces, intenta hacer está tan rapido
as you can, and then pick the course up from there. Everybody else should just do
como puedas, y continúa el curso desde ahí. Todos los demás deben
everything, apart from the occasional optional video like installing for a Mac.
hacer todo , excepto el video esporádico como instalar para Mac
If you don't have one, you skip that, but otherwise, all the videos are there for a purpose.
si no tienes uno, saltalo, pero sino, todos los video tienen un porqué
The learning journey is carefully crafted, and we look forward to taking you from
el viaje didáctico está cuidadosamente trabajado, y ansiamos llevarte desde 0
0... This is very corny! From 0 to hero
a este corner! De 0 a heroe
but that's what we're aiming to do! OK, in the next video we're going to get
pero es lo que queremos hacer! Ok, en el video siguiente vamos a continuar
on and get Unreal downloading and installing. See you soon!
conseguir Unreal descargarlo y instalarlo. Hasta pronto